Select Page

PRIVACY POLICY
--------------

Language Translate

Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at SONOFF Technologies Co., Ltd (“**Company**“, “**we**“, “**us**“, “**our**“). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at support@itead.cc.

When you visit our website [http://sonoff.tech](http://sonoff.tech/) (the “**Website**“), and more generally, use any of our services (the “**Services**“, which include the Website), we appreciate that you are trusting us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy notice, we seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it, and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy notice that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Services immediately.

This privacy notice applies to all information collected through our Services (which, as described above, includes our Website), as well as, any related services, sales, marketing, or events.

**Please read this privacy notice carefully as it will help you understand what we do with the information that we collect.**

#### **Use and Collection of Information:**

[8\. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?](#12)

**1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

**Personal information you disclose to us**

**_In Short:_**  _We collect personal information that you provide to us._

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and services when you participate in activities on the Website or otherwise when you contact us.

The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Website, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect may include the following:

**Personal Information Provided by You.** We collect names; email addresses; phone numbers; usernames; passwords; contact or authentication data; and other similar information.

All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete, and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.

**Information automatically collected**

**_In Short:_**  _Some information — such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and/or browser and device characteristics — is collected automatically when you visit our Website._

We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Website. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser, and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Website and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Website, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.

The information we collect includes:

* _Log and Usage Data._ Log and usage data are service-related, diagnostic, usage, and performance information our servers automatically collect when you access or use our Website and which we record in log files. Depending on how you interact with us, this log data may include your IP address, device information, browser type, and settings, and information about your activity in the Website (such as the date/time stamps associated with your usage, pages, and files viewed, searches and other actions you take such as which features you use), device event information (such as system activity, error reports (sometimes called ‘crash dumps’) and hardware settings).

* _Device Data._ We collect device data such as information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other devices you use to access the Website. Depending on the device used, this device data may include information such as your IP address (or proxy server), device and application identification numbers, location, browser type, hardware model Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, operating system, and system configuration information.

* _Location Data._ We collect location data such as information about your device’s location, which can be either precise or imprecise. How much information we collect depends on the type and settings of the device you use to access the Website. For example, we may use GPS and other technologies to collect geolocation data that tells us your current location (based on your IP address). You can opt-out of allowing us to collect this information either by refusing access to the information or by disabling your Location setting on your device. Note, however, if you choose to opt-out, you may not be able to use certain aspects of the Services.

**2\. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?** 

**_In Short:_**  _We process your information for purposes based on legitimate business interests, the fulfillment of our contract with you, compliance with our legal obligations, and/or your consent._

We use personal information collected via our Website for a variety of business purposes described below. We process your personal information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate business interests, in order to enter into or perform a contract with you, with your consent, and/or for compliance with our legal obligations. We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely on next to each purpose listed below.

We use the information we collect or receive:

* **To facilitate account creation and logon process.** If you choose to link your account with us to a third-party account (such as your Google or Facebook account), we use the information you allowed us to collect from those third parties to facilitate account creation and logon process for the performance of the contract.

* **To post testimonials.** We post testimonials on our Website that may contain personal information. Prior to posting a testimonial, we will obtain your consent to use your name and the content of the testimonial. If you wish to update, or delete your testimonial, please contact us at support@itead.cc and be sure to include your name, testimonial location, and contact information.

* **Request feedback.** We may use your information to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Website.

* **To enable user-to-user communications.** We may use your information in order to enable user-to-user communications with each user’s consent.

* **To manage user accounts.** We may use your information for the purposes of managing our account and keeping it in working order.

* **To send administrative information to you.** We may use your personal information to send you product, service, and new feature information and/or information about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.

* **To protect our Services.** We may use your information as part of our efforts to keep our Website safe and secure (for example, for fraud monitoring and prevention).

* **To enforce our terms, conditions, and policies for business purposes, to comply with legal and regulatory requirements, or in connection with our contract.**

* **To respond to legal requests and prevent harm.** If we receive a subpoena or other legal request, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond.

* **Fulfill and manage your orders.** We may use your information to fulfill and manage your orders, payments, returns, and exchanges made through the Website.

* **Administer prize draws and competitions.** We may use your information to administer prize draws and competitions when you elect to participate in our competitions.

* **To deliver and facilitate the delivery of services to the user.** We may use your information to provide you with the requested service.

* **To respond to user inquiries/offer support to users.** We may use your information to respond to your inquiries and solve any potential issues you might have with the use of our Services.

* **To send you marketing and promotional communications.** We and/or our third-party marketing partners may use the personal information you send to us for our marketing purposes if this is in accordance with your marketing preferences. For example, when expressing an interest in obtaining information about us or our Website, subscribing to marketing, or otherwise contacting us, we will collect personal information from you. You can opt-out of our marketing emails at any time (see the “[WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS](https://app.termly.io/dashboard/website/775898/privacy-policy#privacyrights)” below).

* **Deliver targeted advertising to you.** We may use your information to develop and display personalized content and advertising (and work with third parties who do so) tailored to your interests and/or location and to measure its effectiveness.

* **For other business purposes.** We may use your information for other business purposes, such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Website, products, marketing and your experience. We may use and store this information in aggregated and anonymized form so that it is not associated with individual end users and does not include personal information. We will not use identifiable personal information without your consent.

**3\. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?**

**_In Short:_**  _We only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to provide you with services, to protect your rights, or to fulfill business obligations._

We may process or share your data that we hold based on the following legal basis:

* **Consent:** We may process your data if you have given us specific consent to use your personal information for a specific purpose.

* **Legitimate Interests:** We may process your data when it is reasonably necessary to achieve our legitimate business interests.

* **Performance of a Contract:** Where we have entered into a contract with you, we may process your personal information to fulfill the terms of our contract.

* **Legal Obligations:** We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal processes, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).

* **Vital Interests:** We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

More specifically, we may need to process your data or share your personal information in the following situations:

* **Business Transfers.** We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

* **Vendors, Consultants, and Other Third-Party Service Providers.** We may share your data with third-party vendors, service providers, contractors, or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. Examples include payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and marketing efforts. We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Website, which will enable them to collect data on our behalf about how you interact with our Website over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, pages, or features, and better understand online activity. Unless described in this notice, we do not share, sell, rent, or trade any of your information with third parties for their promotional purposes. We have contracts in place with our data processors, which are designed to help safeguard your personal information. This means that they cannot do anything with your personal information unless we have instructed them to do it. They will also not share your personal information with any organization apart from us. They also commit to protect the data they hold on our behalf and to retain it for the period we instruct.

* **Affiliates.** We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this privacy notice. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.

* **Business Partners.** We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services or promotions.

**4\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?**

**_In Short:_** _We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information._

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our Cookie Notice.

**5\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_** _We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy notice unless otherwise required by law._

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting, or other legal requirements). No purpose in this notice will require us to keep your personal information for longer than 2 years.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize such information or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**6****. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES**

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. At this stage, no uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy notice.

**7\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?**

If you have questions or comments about this notice, you may email us at support@itead.cc or by post to:

SONOFF technologies Co., Ltd

Room 1001, 10F, Building 8, Lianhua Industrial Park, Longyuan Road, Longhua District, Shenzhen, GD

ShenZhen, GuangDong 518000

China

**8\. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?**

Based on the applicable laws of your country, you may have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it in some circumstances. To request to review, update, or delete your personal information, please submit a request form by clicking [here](https://app.termly.io/notify/9b51be7c-c160-44a4-8957-ef906cf3c9bc). We will respond to your request within 30 days.

**BRAND**

**COMPANY**

**SUPPORT**

Subscribe
---------

Get the latest news from SONOFF

Success!
--------

Email 

Copyright © 2024 SONOFF All Rights Reserved. 备案号：[粤ICP备20054679号](https://beian.miit.gov.cn/)  

### Pin It on Pinterest
